<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Couture on RoxTheCasbah</title>
    <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/tags/couture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Couture on RoxTheCasbah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://roxthecasbah.com/en/tags/couture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A nude Black Beauty set</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/black-beauty-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/black-beauty-set/</guid>
      <description>Here I am, back again to talk to you about lingerie making!
 &amp;times;Nude Black Beauty set #1At first, I was not planning to make a set, but I had leftover lace, and I loved the bra so much I though it would be a shame to leave it alone and not give it matching panties.
Bra pattern: Black Beauty Bra, from Emerald Erin Nothing new here, I chose my favorite bra pattern ever, the Black Beauty Bra, the same one I talked about here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Beauty</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/blue-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/blue-beauty/</guid>
      <description>Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about lingerie sewing. If you&amp;rsquo;d have asked me a few back if I planned on sewing lingerie one day, I would have laughed soooo hard! &amp;hellip; And yet!
&amp;times;Blue Beauty #1I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s the same for you, but going lingerie shopping has always been a huge pain for me. I am (fortunately or unfortunately, I don&amp;rsquo;t know) considered as being part of the &amp;ldquo;bigger sizes&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A green needlecord Diego</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/green-diego-needlecord/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/green-diego-needlecord/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love the République du chiffon patterns. I love the style they go for, with a vintage feel to it. And Diego is no exception! But I know that even if I love all of them, there are some of these that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be able to pull off or wouldn&amp;rsquo;t fit me or match what I actually wear. But I can assure you that Diego gets its fair share of wear!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A green striped Pietra</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-green-striped-pietra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-green-striped-pietra/</guid>
      <description>As I told you on my Cielo article, I fell for Pietra, from Closet Core&amp;rsquo;s Rome collection, as soon as I laid eyes on it.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t buy it right away, I let it sit in my mind (and I had other things on my to-make list). But after a few months, I still liked it a lot, so I gave in, and bought the paper version at Metermeter (I don&amp;rsquo;t like assembling PDF for pants&amp;hellip; So many pieces, so little time&amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A high-waisted pants study</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-high-waisted-pants-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-high-waisted-pants-study/</guid>
      <description>A looooong time ago (in a galaxy far, far away), the only ting I was wearing was tight slim jeans. And low waisted jeans&amp;hellip; (*shivers*) I don&amp;rsquo;t want to talk further more about these dark ages, now that I discovered high-waisted pants. And there is nothing else that I would rather wear.
 Where it began On paper, high-waisted pants are a winner: it&amp;rsquo;s comfy, it&amp;rsquo;s got plenty of wiggle room, it shields you from the summer sun and keeps you cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A cropped top study</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-cropped-top-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-cropped-top-study/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back today to talk about this wardrobe staple: the white cropped top.
How it began Noooo, don&amp;rsquo;t leave! Well, I know that cropped tops may remind some of you of the dark ages of the 90s.
And I used to be one of those persons. I always thought it didn&amp;rsquo;t suit me, as I was too short, not thin enough (what beauty standards can make you think&amp;hellip; sighs). But as a matter of fact, now as I started to wear more and more high-waisted pants and shorts and skirts, I began tucking my tees in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, world !</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! Welcome on my brand new shining blog.
This blog is going to be the place where I talk about sewing and knitting mostly. Maybe other DIY stuff if I feel inspired.
My name is Roxanne, I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer by day and crazy sewist and knitter by night. I decided to finally launch this blog, in order to document and share my project.
OK, I know what you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about right now: &amp;lsquo;Blogs are so 2015, now with social media and Instagram, you don&amp;rsquo;t need one of those&amp;hellip;&#39;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
