<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Couture on RoxTheCasbah</title>
    <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/tags/couture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Couture on RoxTheCasbah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://roxthecasbah.com/en/tags/couture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>EN - Ensemble Black Beauty</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/ensemble-black-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/ensemble-black-beauty/</guid>
      <description>Je suis de retour pour te parler (roulement de tambours) &amp;hellip; lingerie ! Surprenant hein ?
 &amp;times;Ensemble Black Beauty #1Je n&amp;rsquo;avais pas prévu de faire un ensemble au départ, mais il me restait de la dentelle, et j&amp;rsquo;aimais tellement le soutien-gorge que je me suis dit que ce serait vraiment dommage de ne pas en faire un ensemble.
Le haut : Black Beauty Bra, d&amp;rsquo;Emerald Erin Bon, rien de nouveau sous le soleil, je suis repartie de mon soutien-gorge chéri, le Black Beauty Bra, dont je vous ai déjà parlé ici.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EN - Blue Beauty</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/blue-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/blue-beauty/</guid>
      <description>Aujourd&amp;rsquo;hui on va parler lingerie. Jusqu&amp;rsquo;à il a quelques années, jamais je n&amp;rsquo;aurais imaginé coudre de la lingerie&amp;hellip; Et pourtant !
&amp;times;Blue Beauty #1Je ne sais pas vous, mais personnellement, les boutiques de lingerie, ça a toujours été la plaie. Ayant la malchance de faire partie des grandes tailles, je ne trouvais jamais quoi que ce soit qui me plaise (sans me coûter un rein j&amp;rsquo;entends)(parce qu&amp;rsquo;un rein contre un soutif, j&amp;rsquo;aurais perdu au change)(et du coup je n&amp;rsquo;aurais pu avoir que 2 soutifs)(BREF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EN - Un Diego en velours vert</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/diego-en-velours-vert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/diego-en-velours-vert/</guid>
      <description>République du chiffon est une marque dont j&amp;rsquo;aime énormément les patrons. J&amp;rsquo;aime beaucoup le style, un brin rétro. Même si j&amp;rsquo;aime leur esthétique, je sais que certains patrons ne correspondent pas forcément à ce que je porte au quotidien et à ce qui me va. Mais pour Diego, j&amp;rsquo;ai flashé au premier coup d’œil !
 &amp;times;Un Diego en velours vert #1Diego le pantalon taille haute Diego est un patron de pantalon taille haute sorti il y a quelques années.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A green striped Pietra</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-green-striped-pietra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 10:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-green-striped-pietra/</guid>
      <description>As I told you on my Cielo article, I fell for Pietra, from Closet Core&amp;rsquo;s Rome collection, as soon as I laid eyes on it.
I didn&amp;rsquo;t buyt it right away, I let it sit in my mind (and I had other things on my to-make list). But after a few months, I still liked it a lot, so I gave in, and bought the paper version at Metermeter (I don&amp;rsquo;t like assembling PDF for pants&amp;hellip; So many pieces, so little time&amp;hellip;)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A high-waisted pants study</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-high-waisted-pants-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-high-waisted-pants-study/</guid>
      <description>A looooong time ago (in a galaxy far, far away), the only ting I was wearing was tight slims jeans. And low waisted jeans&amp;hellip;shivers I don&amp;rsquo;t want to talk further more about these dark ages, now that I discovered high-waisted pants. And there is nothing else that I would like to wear.
 Where it began On paper, the high-waisted pants are a winner: it&amp;rsquo;s comfy, it&amp;rsquo;s got plenty of wiggle room, it shields you from the summer sun and keeps you cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A cropped top study</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-cropped-top-study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/a-cropped-top-study/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back today to talk about this wardrobe staple: the white cropped top.
How it began Noooo, don&amp;rsquo;t leave! Well, I know that cropped tops may remind some of you of the dark ages of the 90s.
And I used to be one of those persons. I always thought it didn&amp;rsquo;t suit me, as I was too short, not thin enough (what beauty standards can make you think&amp;hellip; sighs). But as a matter of fact, now as I started to wear more and more high-waisted pants and shorts and skirts, I began tucking my tees in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello, world !</title>
      <link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! Welcome on my brand new shining blog.
This blog is going to be the place where I talk about sewing and knitting mostly. Maybe other DIY stuff if I feel inspired.
My name is Roxanne, I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer by day and crazy sewist and knitter by night. I decided to finally launch this blog, in order to document and share my project.
OK, I know what you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about right now: &amp;lsquo;Blogs are so 2015, now with social media and Instagram, you don&amp;rsquo;t need one of those&amp;hellip;&#39;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
