<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lingerie on RoxTheCasbah</title><link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/tags/lingerie/</link><description>Recent content in lingerie on RoxTheCasbah</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://roxthecasbah.com/en/tags/lingerie/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Choosing a pattern and the materials, bra sew along #1</title><link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/choosing-the-pattern-and-the-materials/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/choosing-the-pattern-and-the-materials/</guid><description>What better way to start this sew along by talking about the first step in any sewing project: the pattern. This step is really important because it will allow you to know what materials and notions you need to gather.
Choosing a patterns There are sooooo many patterns out there this day&amp;hellip; The hardest part is to only chose one!
I would advise you to start with something close to the shape you like to wear:</description></item><item><title>Let's do a bra sew along</title><link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/let-s-do-a-bra-sew-along/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/let-s-do-a-bra-sew-along/</guid><description>Sewing a bra can be scary. I know a lot of people who are afraid to try because they&amp;rsquo;re intimidated by elastics, underwires, finding the right size, wasting away fabrics and notions, etc. It&amp;rsquo;s funny because, personally, I find it more difficult to sew a coat or a pair of jeans than sewing a bra. That&amp;rsquo;s the reason why I&amp;rsquo;ll try with this series of blog posts to divide it into sizeable chunks that will make the whole process less scary for you.</description></item><item><title>Something about underwired bra fitting</title><link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/underwired-bra-fitting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/underwired-bra-fitting/</guid><description>A few weeks ago, Milena from Eclipse lingerie studio launched a book about lingerie sewing. It&amp;rsquo;s very complete and contains everything you need to sew yourself a full lingerie wardrobe, from a simple triangle bralette to high-waisted panties, including a sports bra and an underwired bra. And on top of it all (as if it wasn&amp;rsquo;t already enough), the pictures are great, far from the &amp;ldquo;traditional&amp;rdquo; lingerie pictures, but with real people&amp;rsquo;s bodies (and it feels good).</description></item><item><title>Flowery black silk set</title><link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/flowery-black-silk-set/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/flowery-black-silk-set/</guid><description>I looooove sewing bras. (You don&amp;rsquo;t say?!) I know, it&amp;rsquo;s no secret. But I wish I could say the same about panties&amp;hellip; but I find it boring. But I still need panties in my life (I know I could live without them, I know some people do)(but that&amp;rsquo;s not the life I want to live)(I&amp;rsquo;m putting an end to that debate now). And I love lingerie sets. So I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to sew a pair of panties each time I sew a bra.</description></item><item><title>A nude Black Beauty set</title><link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/black-beauty-set/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/black-beauty-set/</guid><description>Here I am, back again to talk to you about lingerie making!
&amp;times; Nude Black Beauty set #1 At first, I was not planning to make a set, but I had leftover lace, and I loved the bra so much I though it would be a shame to leave it alone and not give it matching panties.
Bra pattern: Black Beauty Bra, from Emerald Erin Nothing new here, I chose my favorite bra pattern ever, the Black Beauty Bra, the same one I talked about in a previous post.</description></item><item><title>Blue Beauty</title><link>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/blue-beauty/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://roxthecasbah.com/en/post/blue-beauty/</guid><description>Today we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about lingerie sewing. If you&amp;rsquo;d have asked me a few back if I planned on sewing lingerie one day, I would have laughed soooo hard! &amp;hellip; And yet!
&amp;times; Blue Beauty #1 I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it&amp;rsquo;s the same for you, but going lingerie shopping has always been a huge pain for me. I am (fortunately or unfortunately, I don&amp;rsquo;t know) considered as being part of the &amp;ldquo;bigger sizes&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>